

Electronic Engineer with specialization in Software Engineer. Experience in development electronic products. Well-versed in microcontrollers using C language and libraries from this ecosystem, hardware development and PCB designer. Studying electronic since 2010 become an active member of the maker community in Brazil. Currently developing new projects based on FPGA.

VINICIUS MYLONAS

Phone:

+ 55 11 98164 2053

E-Mail:

vinimyls@hotmail.com

Linkedin:

linkedin.com/in/vinicius-mylonas/

Nationality:

Brazilian

Skill Highlights

- Over 8 years practical experience
- Knowledge in PCB ECAD
- C for MCUs
- FPGA:
 - VHDL
 - Quartus II
 - ModelSim
- Curious about new technologies
- Protocols RS485/RS232, others
- Project manager
- FPGA enthusiast
- Strong IT skills
- 3D modeling and printing

Languages

Portuguese - Native

English – B1 (McGraw Hill certificate)

Spanish – A2 (McGraw Hill certificate)

German - A1 (McGraw Hill certificate)

Experience

01/2020 - Current

Electronic Engineer - Verin Fire Alarm, São Paulo, Brazil

- Developer of new products for fire alarm systems with STM32, PIC16xx PIC12xx, ESP8266.
- Maintenance department management.
- PTH to SMD migration and development.

01/2012 - 12/2019

Electronic Technician - Verin Fire Alarm, São Paulo, Brazil

- Maintenance of equipment on bench and on site.
- PCB designer.
- Technical support for consumers and sales department.

01/2018 - Current

Member Volunteer at the Brazilian Fire Safety Committee

- Discussing the standards currents in national scenery proposing changes and adaptations.
- Search and translate foreigners standards.

Education

2020 - 2021

Specialization in Software Engineer

PUC-SP / São Paulo, Brazil

2014-2019

Bachelor of Electronic Engineer

Universidade São Judas Tadeu / São Paulo, Brazil

2010-2011

Technical Couse in Electronic Systems

ETEC Professor Horácio Augusto da Silveira / São Paulo, Brazil